Justin Katic

Programmer

Address Sydney, NSW Phone 0418814568 E-mail justinkaticdev@gmail.com Website https://justinkatic.com LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/justin-katic/

Highly educated programmer with commitment to excellence and more than two years of experience. Effective trouble-shooter promoting C# and C++ skills. Extensive understanding of game development.

Work History

2020-11 - Current

Programmer JEAH! Studio, Sydney, NSW

- Wrote highly maintainable, solid code, forming core framework.
- Put together a team to create a published project on both IOS and Android.
- •Solo programmer working with both artists and designers.

Lich Legend Android

Lich Legend Apple

2020-04 - Current

Cert II Junior Tutor Academy of Interactive Entertainment, Sydney, NSW

- •Helped faculty and staff in duties such as teaching classes, conducting orientation programs, and issuing transcripts.
- Provided knowledge to students studying Cert II programming.
- Maintained inclusive learning environment to enable students to gain maximum benefit from lessons.

2013-03 - 2021-02

Warehouse Operator Aldi, Sydney, NSW

- Evaluated supplies and product inventory to check for quality and quantity issues and returned unacceptable materials to vendors.
- •Operated pallet jacks and material moving equipment to receive and transport items from various warehouse locations.
- •Used forklifts and pallet jacks to relocate products.
- •Verified accuracy of shipping and receiving documents and maintained records.

Projects

2021-07 – Current

Programmer Dead Bear Studio, Sydney, NSW

- •Streamline deployment process by developing continuous integration tools.
- •Streamline open-source programming assets into projects to shorten development times and enhance software compatibility.
- Ensuring networking code is always optimized and clear.
- Write highly maintainable, solid code, forming core framework.

Programmer Pyrite Studio, Sydney, NSW

- •Worked with cross-functional design teams to create software solutions that elevated client-side experience and significantly improved overall functionality and performance.
- •Wrote highly maintainable, solid code, forming core framework.
- •Streamlined deployment process by developing continuous integration tools.

Education

2021-02- Current	Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development: Programming Academy of Interactive Entertainment -Sydney
2020-02- 2020-11	Diploma of Digital and Interactive Games: Programming Academy of Interactive Entertainment -Sydney
2017-04- 2017-11	Certificate IV Game Design: Game Design TAFE NSW-Illawarra

Skills

- C#
- Unity Engine
- Testing/Debugging

- Source Control
- C++
- Unreal Engine

References

References available upon request.